<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Welcome on Uppertonic</title>
    <link>https://uppertonic.co.uk/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Welcome on Uppertonic</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>(c) Uppertonic Hypnotherapy</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://uppertonic.co.uk/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>A New Start</title>
      <link>https://uppertonic.co.uk/blog/mindset/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://uppertonic.co.uk/blog/mindset/</guid>
      <description>Starting with you Are you back into your usual routine? Perhaps there seem to be so many tasks on your plate, your head feels in the clouds. Perhaps you want something to change but you just can&amp;rsquo;t see how. When it&amp;rsquo;s a bit foggy it can seem easier to carry on as usual. If you&amp;rsquo;ve read this far, you&amp;rsquo;ve already stopped for a few moments and maybe curious to start making that difference&amp;hellip; easily.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Privacy Policy</title>
      <link>https://uppertonic.co.uk/privacypolicy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://uppertonic.co.uk/privacypolicy/</guid>
      <description>Statement of Intent This privacy policy sets out how Uppertonic Hypnotherapy uses and protects the information you provide when accessing my website. I intend to ensure any data you provide is kept secure, managed respectfully and only used for the purposes for which it has been provided.
Contact details Name: Amanda Upperton E-mail: Amanda@Uppertonic.co.uk Website: Uppertonic.co.uk
You can visit this website without revealing any information about yourself. However, there may be occasions where you are asked to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, such as using the contact form.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About me</title>
      <link>https://uppertonic.co.uk/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://uppertonic.co.uk/about/</guid>
      <description>Amanda Upperton, MNCH(Reg.), Clinical Hypnotherapist
I support people making positive change and I&amp;rsquo;m passionate about helping others to help themselves.
For decades, I thrived in my IT career alongside my life of family, friends, hobbies and interests. BUT… life became quite complex from juggling family responsibilities alongside work, the loss of loved ones and striving to keep everything in my world moving along. Self-care became challenging, unhelpful emotions and physical problems started to emerge.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Services</title>
      <link>https://uppertonic.co.uk/services/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://uppertonic.co.uk/services/</guid>
      <description>HYPNOSIS How many times have you become engrossed in a good book or film? It&amp;rsquo;s easy to lose track of time if it&amp;rsquo;s really absorbing, isn&amp;rsquo;t it? That&amp;rsquo;s an example of focused attention.
Hypnosis is a completely natural state of focused attention. We might enter this state several times a day and will have experienced it reading a good book, watching a film, doing various activities, going on a journey and in many other ways.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://uppertonic.co.uk/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://uppertonic.co.uk/contact/</guid>
      <description>Please send me a message using the form below. </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
